(Sheldon:)...with the memory of my grandparents,
Mee-Maw and Pop-Pop...
...singing carols,
while I sat in front of the fire...
(Sheldon:)...and tried to build a high-energy particle
accelerator out of Legos.
- Okay, continuing the quest...
- Wait, there's still four more verses.
(Sheldon:)You don't sing a song and not finish it.
(Sheldon:)Hither, page, and stand by me
If thou know'st it, telling
(Sheldon:)Yonder peasant, who is he?
Where and what his dwelling?
(Sheldon:)Brightly shone the moon that night
Though the frost was...
- It looks like he's doing pretty good.
- Of course he is.
(Penny:)That girl just got dumped by her boyfriend,
she's angry, she's drunk...
(Penny:)...and her favorite movie
is Slumdog Millionaire.
(Amy:)That is some low-hanging fruit.
(Bernadette:)Oh, here he comes.
- So, how'd it go?
- Great.
(Raj:)I bought her a couple of drinks
and she gave me her e-mail address.
(Raj:)Ooh!
"Jennifer at not even if you were
the last guy on Earth dot loser."